<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Michele&#39;s Piece of Mind</title>
    <link>https://mnalli.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Michele&#39;s Piece of Mind</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <managingEditor>michelenalli96@gmail.com (Michele Nalli)</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>michelenalli96@gmail.com (Michele Nalli)</webMaster>
    <atom:link href="https://mnalli.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Express.js Interactive REPL</title>
      <link>https://mnalli.github.io/posts/express-interactive-repl/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 09:26:07 +0200</pubDate><author>michelenalli96@gmail.com (Michele Nalli)</author>
      <guid>https://mnalli.github.io/posts/express-interactive-repl/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Having an interactive REPL is one of those things that makes experimenting and debugging so much nicer. Django has it built-in, through the manage.py shell command. This is basically the Python REPL with Django context preloaded. Express does not have anything like that built-in, but it is easy to implement it.&#xA;All code snippets shown will reference this tutorial project.&#xA;TL;DR # javascript node --interactive --eval &amp;#34;`cat init-context.js`&amp;#34; # typescript ts-node --interactive --eval &amp;#34;`cat init-context.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Automatic graph generation with Graphviz</title>
      <link>https://mnalli.github.io/posts/graphviz-tutorial/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 23:33:26 +0100</pubDate><author>michelenalli96@gmail.com (Michele Nalli)</author>
      <guid>https://mnalli.github.io/posts/graphviz-tutorial/</guid>
      <description>Visualizing data is a fantastic way to gain insights into a specific domain. In some contexts, it would be beneficial to be able to generate a graph programmatically.&#xA;Graphviz Graphviz is a graph visualization tool (I bet you wouldn&amp;rsquo;t have guessed that, would you?). It reads a textual description of a graph written in its Domain Specific Language, called DOT , and is capable of producing various output formats, including images.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Install MS Teams for Linux as a PWA</title>
      <link>https://mnalli.github.io/posts/ms-teams-chromium-pwa/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Feb 2025 20:54:30 +0100</pubDate><author>michelenalli96@gmail.com (Michele Nalli)</author>
      <guid>https://mnalli.github.io/posts/ms-teams-chromium-pwa/</guid>
      <description>On my work computer (Ubuntu 24.04) I had Microsoft Teams installed using flatpak , which is a wrapper around the webapp executed in chromium. As I have two accounts (one for my company and one for my client), I would like to be able to have both accounts open at the same time. I solved this issue by running a second instance of the webapp directly in chromium (not my main browser), in app mode (using the --app switch).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Intune on Ubuntu 24.04 LTS</title>
      <link>https://mnalli.github.io/posts/ms-intune-ubuntu/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 19:38:28 +0100</pubDate><author>michelenalli96@gmail.com (Michele Nalli)</author>
      <guid>https://mnalli.github.io/posts/ms-intune-ubuntu/</guid>
      <description>As we can see in the official installation guide , as of today 25/11/2024, the Microsoft Intune app is not available for Ubuntu 24.04 (noble).&#xA;We can verify this by searching for intune-platform in the package list of microsoft repository for Ubuntu 22.04 and 24.04:&#xA;jammy: https://packages.microsoft.com/ubuntu/22.04/prod/dists/jammy/main/binary-amd64/Packages noble: https://packages.microsoft.com/ubuntu/24.04/prod/dists/noble/main/binary-amd64/Packages As of today, you will find it only in the first one.&#xA;Follow the official installation guide for Ubuntu 22.04, then come back here.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
